<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Saurabh Mittal</title>
    <link>https://saurabhmittal16.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Saurabh Mittal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 22:00:35 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://saurabhmittal16.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>UTCTF recur challenge</title>
      <link>https://saurabhmittal16.github.io/posts/2021/03/utctf-recur-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 22:00:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saurabhmittal16.github.io/posts/2021/03/utctf-recur-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend, I participated in the UTCTF 2021 but was unable to spend a lot of time on the challenges. One of the challenge I worked on was the recur challenge in the Reverse Engineering category. The challenge was not that hard but I had fun working on it so I decided to write a writeup for the challenge.
The challenge had a binary file attached with it and the description of the challenge was -</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WPICTF pwn</title>
      <link>https://saurabhmittal16.github.io/posts/2020/04/wpictf-pwn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 21:52:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saurabhmittal16.github.io/posts/2020/04/wpictf-pwn/</guid>
      <description>I participated in the WPICTF over the weekend and it was a great experience. The challenges were fun and hard enough to keep things interesting. I solved a few challenges but the part that makes me happy is that I solved 2 out of the 4 pwn problems. In this post, I will explain how I solved the two pwns - dorsia1 and dorsia3.
dorsia1 The source codes of some of the challenges were placed in a video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ROP Emporium - Pivot Writeup</title>
      <link>https://saurabhmittal16.github.io/posts/2020/04/rop-emporium-pivot-writeup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 22:00:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saurabhmittal16.github.io/posts/2020/04/rop-emporium-pivot-writeup/</guid>
      <description>I recently came across the ropemporium challenges while looking for resources to learn Return Oriented Programming (ROP). I think that the challenges are very good and the difficulty increases with the problems which keep things interesting. The challenge this writeup is about is the pivot challenge. I will be using the 32 bit binary for the explanation purpose but the solution is pretty much the same for the 64-bit version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>https://saurabhmittal16.github.io/posts/2020/03/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 13:06:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saurabhmittal16.github.io/posts/2020/03/first-post/</guid>
      <description>Hello friend, welcome to my blog. I will use this blog for articles about projects I am working on or for CTF writeups of challenges</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://saurabhmittal16.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saurabhmittal16.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I am Saurabh Mittal. I am currently pursuing my Bachelors in Technology, Computer Science Engineering, from Delhi Technological University. I am a Full Stack Developer with experience in web app development.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a few things I have worked with -
 ReactJS NodeJS MongoDB HTML/CSS/JavaScript Python Flutter  I build stuff for fun, some which are available on my Github profile. Some of my projects can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://saurabhmittal16.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saurabhmittal16.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>Event Scraper A web scraper built with Puppeteer to scrape and store information of various events (from Facebook) organised by different societies and clubs inside the university. The store information is distributed using a mobile app.
 Stone Paper Scissors Game A multiplayer Stone Paper Scissors game where two players can play against each other by passing the generated link to the other player and compete. Built with Web Sockets and React.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
